const quizzes = [
{category: "history",
questions: [
  {
  question: "What year did the Civil War end?",
  options: ["1900", "1749", "1861","1865", "1910"],
  correctChoice: 3,  
},
{
question: "Joan of Arc is from which country?",
options: ["England", "Italy", "Mexico","France", "Greece"],
correctChoice: 3,  
},
{
  question: "What is the name of the war that came right after Desert Storm?",
  options: ["Korean War", "WWII", "Persian Gulf War", "Iraq War", "None of the Above"],
  correctChoice: 2,
},
{
  question: "What year did the Cambodian genocide start",
  options: ["1920", "1600", "1980","1910", "1975"],
  correctChoice: 3,  
},
{
  question: "Which country had the potato famine between 1845 and 1852?",
  options: ["Scotland", "India", "Peru","Wales", "Ireland"],
  correctChoice: 4,
},
{
  question: "Elizabeth I was the daughter of which famous king?",
  options: ["Henry VIII", "Louis IX", "Philip II","Alexander the Great", "Louis XIV"],
  correctChoice: 0,  
},
{
  question: "What was the name of the period in Russia that had the removal of the monarchy and the adoption of socialism?",
  options: ["Socialist Reform", "Russian Revolution", "Russian Socialist Period","WWII", "Great Purge"],
  correctChoice: 1,  
},
{
  question: "Who was the 12th president of the US",
  options: ["Zachary Taylor", "James Madison", "Andrew Jackson","FDR", "Joe Burns"],
  correctChoice: 0,  
},
{
  question: "Which country has the highest population in the world?",
  options: ["Pakistan", "USA", "Russia","China", "Vietnam"],
  correctChoice: 3,  
},
{
question: "What then country was the birthplace of Christianity",
options: ["Macedonia", "Judea", "Egypt","Iberia", "Persia"],
correctChoice: 1,  
},
]
}
{category: "popculture",
  questions: [
    {
    question: "What year was the release of Thriller by Michael Jackson?",
    options: ["1990", "1972", "1982","1998", "1950"],
    correctChoice: 2,  
  },
  {
  question: "What is the name of the famous Christmas movie featuring Macaulay Caulken?",
  options: ["Home Alone", "Jingle All The Way", "White Christmas","Elf", "Bug's Life"],
  correctChoice: 0,  
  },
  {
    question: "Super Mario is a platform game series created by which company?",
    options: ["Nintendo", "Play Station", "Sega", "Game Boy", "Atari"],
    correctChoice: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What year was the first Hershey bar sold?",
    options: ["1920", "1900", "1980","2000", "1930"],
    correctChoice: 1,  
  },
  {
    question: "What color is not on the Pepsi logo?",
    options: ["Blue", "Red", "Orange","White", "Black"],
    correctChoice: 2,
  },
  {
    question: "Which state is known for it's oranges?",
    options: ["California", "Kentucky", "Hawaii","Florida", "Nebraska"],
    correctChoice: 3,  
  },
  {
    question: "What month is St. Patrick's Day?",
    options: ["March", "April", "February", "May", "December"],
    correctChoice: 0,  
  },
  {
    question: "Which English girl group started in the 90s?",
    options: ["En Vogue", "Salt-N-Peppa", "*NSYNC","Spice Girls", "Ace of Base"],
    correctChoice: 3,  
  },
  {
    question: "Which doll was introduced in 1959",
    options: ["Polly Pocket", "Barbie", "Cabbage Patch","Legos", "American Girl"],
    correctChoice: 1,  
  },
  {
  question: "What series is Pikachu in?",
  options: ["Digimon", "Seasame Street", "Yu-Gi-Oh!","Power Puff Girls", "Pokemon"],
  correctChoice: 4,  
  },
  ]
  }
];
